pubget.com 2015-12-06

# Search engine for life-science PDFs - Pubget

EffectiveNov 30, 2012

By using the www.pubget.com Web site or any other Web-based service of Pubget Corporation (“Pubget”), you agree to the terms of the Pubget Online Privacy Policy, as set forth below.

#### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

As with most Web sites, Pubget collects information about your visits to our sites for purposes of supporting, tailoring and improving your experience. We also use this information for purposes of helping us show advertisements on our Web site and other Web sites that, based on your information, are likely to be interesting to you. Some of this information is collected automatically through the use of “cookies” or other technology whenever you visit our Web sites. More information on Pubget’s use of those technologies and the types of information collected is provided below.

In addition, when you engage in certain activities on Pubget’s Web sites, such as purchasing documents through the Pubget PaperStore, or requesting or obtaining services which require activation and/or registration, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself and/or your organization by filling out and submitting a form, or by otherwise providing us with the requested information. Such information will be used to make the relevant materials, features or services available to you and, if applicable, others within your organization.

Should you choose to take advantage of our services, we may require that you provide us with personal information, such as your name, organization name, mailing address, e-mail address and other identifying information. Should you choose to pay with a credit card, you may be asked to provide a card number, expiration date and the name and address of the cardholder. For more information about data security, please see the Security section of this Privacy Policy.

It is completely optional for you to provide the requested information and/or to engage in these activities. Should you choose not to do so, however, it may not be possible for Pubget to provide the particular materials, features or services that you are seeking.

Pubget collects all of this information in order to record and support your usage and content purchase transactions and your use of the applicable Pubget services and other associated activities on our Web sites and to display advertisements for products and services that may be interesting to you. For example, we may use the information you provide to record and reflect your preferences, to verify the details of a document order placed by you or to keep you informed about our or our affiliates’ or business partners’ products and services. Or we may use such information to make content recommendations to you based on your prior searches or to show advertisements for relevant Pubget products, services or features on third party websites that you visit. Pubget may supplement the information you provide with commercially available demographic and address information in order to enhance our and our affiliates’ ability to serve you.

#### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Pubget shares the information that you provide to us in accordance with our obligations to copyright rightsholders and vendors of data and materials made accessible through Pubget’s Web sites and related products and services. These obligations may vary from program to program. Details about such obligations under any particular Pubget program are available upon request. Pubget does NOT, however, share credit card details with such copyright rightsholders or vendors (other than third party credit card processing companies used in applicable Pubget services). Nor does Pubget share specific transaction information with such rightsholders or vendors regarding the use of data or materials of other rightsholders or vendors.

Pubget may reuse, share or resell certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our Web sites. We may, for example, provide your organization name and anonymized information regarding your prior searches to an advertiser that utilizes our advertising services where you have indicated interest in one of that advertiser’s products; or we may use your data combined with that of other users to create anonymized reports on usage or industry trends. Any such information will only be shared in a form which does not include any personally identifiable information.

If you have identified yourself, or are identified by your employer to Pubget as being associated with a Pubget-participating institution or organization, you may receive promotional communications from Pubget or its affiliates, either directly from us or through your participating institution or organization. Further, when you use your organization's credit card or Pubget billing account to transact business with us, the organization will receive information about the materials you have used and reported to Pubget. Similarly, in circumstances where multiple individuals associated with the same organization share a single account or a single user name and password, each individual may have access to information provided by the other individuals on the same account.

Please note that we may use outside vendors to fulfill document orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies retain, share, store and use the personally identifiable information that they receive from Pubget for purposes of providing such services, and not for other purposes. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information or other information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process.

Pubget recognizes and appreciates the importance of the responsible use of your personal information. Except as disclosed above or in published lists of customers, we do not release or sell lists of our customer names to outside organizations. Further, your personal information is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access to it. Finally, when you submit personal information to Pubget, you understand and agree that Pubget and its affiliates and trusted vendors may transfer, store and process your customer profile in any country in which we do business, including but not limited to the United States. Please be advised that Pubget is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any other Web sites to which pubget.com or any other Pubget Web site may link.

#### USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

Pubget utilizes web analytics tools (including third party tools such as Google Analytics) that automatically collect non-personally-identifiable information from your browser whenever you interact with our site, through the use of “cookies” or similar technology. A cookie is a small string of data that is transferred to your browser from a Web site and can only be read by the Web site that gave it to you. The cookie acts as an identification card which identifies your browser and tracks and records your preferences and helps us improve our services and your experience. The cookie cannot be executed as software code or used to deliver viruses. We also use cookies when you interact with services we offer to our affiliates and business partners, such as the advertising services we offer on pubget.com, and certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits may be tracked by such cookies and shared with such affiliates and partners – for example, in order to allow our advertisers to monitor the usage of their advertisements and to better serve and offer relevant advertisements. Information collected through cookies or similar technology may also be used to help Pubget and our affiliates display advertisements on other sites (including Google and other sites within the Google Display Network) that you visit in order to inform you of products, services or features of Pubget or our affiliates that we think will be interesting to you. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google [Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences). You can also opt out of certain third-party vendors’ use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to accept it or not. Pubget's Web-based offerings include a few Web pages that are inaccessible without a cookie. These pages are associated with an automated log-in feature that allows you to access your account information while bypassing the need to provide your identity and password each time. You are not required to use the automated log-in feature. Choosing not to use it will not affect your ability to use any other part of our Web-based offerings or to use Pubget's general services. In the event that Pubget decides to create other Web-based offerings that are inaccessible without a cookie (which Pubget reserves the right to do), you will be given the option to accept the cookie necessary for such access.

As with most Web sites, Pubget also gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, a date/time stamp and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not include personally identifiable information, to analyze trends, administer the site track users' movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We also employ a software technology called pixel tags (also known as Web beacons) that help us better manage content on our Web site and in other electronic communications by indicating what content is most effective. Pixel tags are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer's hard drive, pixel tags are embedded invisibly in Web pages and in other electronic communications.

When you accept our cookies, we use them to track your visit to any Pubget Web offering. In addition, we use log files and clear gifs to help manage our Web site and other electronic communications. However, none of this information, other than the automated log-in feature, identifies you personally or is tied to any of your personally identifiable information. Pubget does not associate any of this information with personally identifiable information unless you have provided it to us.

#### CHANGING OUR RECORDS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have the right to correct your personal information. This may be accomplished either directly on our Web site on those screens that allow you to edit your personal information; by writing to Pubget at:

Pubget Corporation  
ATTN: Privacy Manager  
2 Liberty Square, 2nd Floor  
Boston, Massachusetts 02109  
privacy@pubget.com

When you contact us please include your name, address and/or e-mail address, account number (if known) and a detailed explanation of your request.

#### OPTING OUT OF RECEIVING INFORMATION

Pubget follows industry standard safe unsubscribe practices. You have the right to opt out of receiving marketing communications and newsletters from Pubget by following the "unsubscribe" instructions that come with each message from us or our affiliates. In addition, you may opt out of receiving such communications by writing to the Privacy Manager using the information provided above.

#### SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us. The password that protects your personal information, as well as your credit card information, are encrypted during transmission using secure socket layer (SSL) technology, which is widely used on the Internet for this purpose. These data are also stored in encrypted form.

Pubget adheres to generally accepted industry standards to protect this information, both during transmission and once we receive it. These standards include the use of leading hardware and software applications. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your applicable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can e-mail us at [privacy@pubget.com](mailto:privacy@pubget.com) or contact our Privacy Manager at the address listed above. 

If at any time you believe that we have not adhered to this privacy policy or you have a complaint regarding the way your personal information is being handled, please contact the Privacy Manager using the contact information provided above. Disputes under this privacy policy will be resolved by the Privacy Manager, who will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly investigate and, if necessary, correct any problem.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

When we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on the homepage of www.pubget.com for 30 days that the policy has been updated and by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated.
